Hi everyone, welcome back to the podcast.
Today, we’re diving deep into the topic of productivity.
Why do some people get more done in 24 hours than others?
Well, it starts with understanding energy management.
We often mistake being busy with being productive.
Actually, multitasking can reduce efficiency.
So today, we'll break down how to prioritize tasks effectively.
We'll also talk about the myth of hustle culture.
You know, working non-stop doesn’t always lead to better results.
Sometimes, it leads to burnout, anxiety, and fatigue.
To help with this, we brought on productivity coach Emma Rivera.
She’s trained over 1,000 professionals in time management.
Emma, welcome to the show.
Thanks so much for having me, I'm excited to be here.
Let’s start with what productivity actually means.
Sure! Productivity is about maximizing meaningful output.
It’s not about doing more things, but doing the right things.
And making sure you have time for rest and reflection.
That’s such a good reminder. I think we all need that.
Let’s dive into techniques like time-blocking and deep work.